This is how I'll become.
Supreme Commander!
A hero!
This is my story!
I've seen a dream.
It's not even a dream.
It's not a dream.
I'd like to see it.
When I was in the moment.
You were me and connected.
And I'm ready to go.
I'm ready to go.
And we'll be all this way. And
we'll be all this way for you.
I will be all this world in the sky.
We will never be anything.
I'll be all this time.
I'll be all
this
way.
So that's what she meant
by physically demanding?
No fair.
Things are really starting to heat up!
Coming up next in round two, we have Shushu
Tsuruka of the 7th Squadron! Hell yeah!
Versus Sahara Wakata of the 6th!
Both competitors specialize
in hand-to-hand combat!
I have a feeling this is
gonna be an entire battle!
Watch this, Yuki, I'm
about to clobber her!
Okay!
And then maybe you'll show
me some appreciation after?
Uh...
Huh?
Hmm.
Yeah, Shiho, since you lost your
match, you get to be our cheerleader.
Good luck, Sahara, you got this.
You can count on me, I'll make you proud.
Since we both like close combat, why don't
we hold off on our abilities until later?
Okay.
Ready, set, let the battle begin!
Here I come!
Sahara sets up with a gracious kick, But
Shushu grabs her by the leg and slams her!
She follows it up with an elbow drop!
Sahara grabs Shushu from behind
and hits her with a German Suplex!
It's not over yet!
I'm so tired.
That was long enough.
Bring out the ability! Already?
It was just starting to get good!
Fine, you're gonna get it!
What number do you think she'll do?
Just one or maybe two?
I would guess three or so.
Both of their abilities center
around physical strength.
This'll be a short match.
Paradigm Shift!
Ha! Yeah!
Oh, my!
That's so neat!
Okay, it's my turn!
Crazy shape!
On three!
One, two!
Huh?
Paper beats!
I win rock, paper, scissors!
You totally cheated.
Sahara unleashed her
awesome crazy shape ability!
It allows her to boost
her strength for the
precise amount of time
she sets in advance!
One minute minimum, 60 maximum!
The shorter the time allotted,
the stronger she gets!
However, her ability has a mandatory
three-minute Golden period!
Nice move!
Keep it up, Sahara!
Why, you?
You're silent and impressive,
but it makes you easy to die!
Huh?
And it makes you an easy target!
Ah!
Shuzu?
Yuki, you don't have to give me that look.
Well, are you ready to give up now?
Me give up?
You've gotta be joking.
I've only begun to show you what I can do!
Oh, wow, you've really got guts!
It's weird to me, too.
Why am I so determined?
Come on, Shushu.
Having a boyfriend is fun.
Jeez, you sound like a broken record.
I just don't get why
you're so opposed to it.
There's never a dull moment with him.
And seeing that look of joy on his face,
it's the best feeling in the world.
Whoa, it's rare to find a girl
so devoted to her man nowadays.
You're so old-fashioned.
You do you, but I'm not interested
in romance with some guy.
I'm looking for something more exciting.
I've been thinking about
joining these guys lately.
If I went to Mato, I
bet I'd never get bored.
Every single day would be a total blast.
Very on brand. Isn't it?
I guess you just don't understand
what I'm going through.
But you'll get it one of these days.
Yuki, keep your eyes on me.
Cause I'm about to win!
Don't you think you'd have an easier
time moving around if you were smaller?
It's important to assess the situation
and tailor your ability accordingly!
You think smaller is better?
That kind of self-control
is a snooze fest!
I live by one motto!
Go big or go home! Get ready!
Let's paradigm shift!
I'll push the envelope and crush you!
I didn't see that coming! And... Going!
I was too big for you to dodge, wasn't I?
Take this!
Hey, Ref, can you see
if she's unconscious?
Uh-huh, sure!
She did it!
Miss Shushu won her match! Yeah!
One!
Two!
Huh?
She got back up?
That's part of Sahara's ability!
If she loses consciousness
while her skill is active,
her heightened killer
instinct takes control.
and will continue to fight on its own!
She'll attack enemies and allies alike,
but it only makes her
that much more powerful.
Tahara can sleep anytime, anywhere.
That happens to be her secret weapon.
One!
Two!
Three!
It's all over, folks!
The winner is...
Tahara Wakasa!
All because of my incredible
cheerleading skills!
She took her down in three minutes, Vlad.
Shushu!
How are you feeling?
There's no need to worry.
I got her all patched up.
Oh, no!
Your shirt ripped!
Huh?
Sahara, get the hell off me, dammit!
I must've...
Here, take this! Shushu! Huh? Our nom!
Commander...
I'm so sorry for losing my match.
You almost had her.
We will discuss where
you can improve later.
I think you better go get changed. Sure.
I was like an idiot, and
Yuki saw the whole thing!
Shushu?
Um, do you want anything to drink?
I can grab it for you
while you get dressed.
No, I'm okay.
If there's anything I
can do, just let me know.
I am the caretaker.
Can you take care of my memories and
erase that pitiful excuse for a match?
I think it sucks you didn't win, but
I don't think it was pitiful at all.
You mean it?
To be perfectly honest, I wanted to see
more of the wrestling you did at the start.
You would've, if she
hadn't been a buzzkill.
Hey, Yuki?
Uh...
Can you close your eyes for a sec?
Uh, sure.
Mm-hmm.
Hey, Shushu!
To be fair, I did tell
you to close your eyes.
Okay, but why the hell did you kiss me?
Well, I...
Uh... Hmm.
Uh...
I figured I would chase the shock
of losing with an even bigger shock!
That's the power move!
Uh...
I can't tell him how I feel
until I get him to like me more.
Any anomalies in Mato? Nay?
No.
There's nothing out of the...
Huh?
A spy?
Wow, we only just broke our cover.
Not bad.
Tell the others I said hi, and
that the battle begins now.
Who was that? What's wrong?
Did you see something?
I...
Shuki, where in the world
are they coming from?
Don't worry, you can relax.
My barrier is impenetrable.
This flimsy thing is a barrier?
A humanoid?
I am Riren and this absurdity
fills me with laughter!
No way!
That thing cracked my barrier!
We're calling off the exhibition.
What a bunch of pests!
It's about time you went extinct!
You're a dying breed!
All hands prepare for battle!
Tenka! I'm on it.
I'll take the non-combatants
back to the dorm.
And have Nei give you her recon report!
Destroy every last Shuki! Yes, ma 'am!
I'll handle this one on my own!
Commander!
Shushu!
Can you fight? Yeah!
Paradigm Shift!
Taste my boot!
I'm already feeling as good as new!
Like this!
Don't let up on the crowd control!
I'll cover your six!
No, not them.
Going somewhere?
I'm your opponent.
Not you either.
But perhaps I'll burn you down to a crisp.
Oh?
Yachio, are you all right?
He's gonna be a tough one to crack.
Just now, you stepped in because you knew
the lightning was coming ahead of time.
You bastard!
You'll pay for that!
Commander!
Let me ride on Yuki's
back with you! With her?
Two people at the same time?
But we've never tried that before!
All right, get on!
Huh?
You can trust me.
Let's go.
The three of us. Right!
I've got a gut feeling.
That with two masters,
he'll take on a more powerful form.
so what do you think yuki
ready to use new powers
let's give them hell
power is coursing through
I bet I could do it now.
That move she did back then.
I'll use the same Methodist
Brand Break to channel my energy!
Howling Blast!
So that's what two can do! Perfect!
Now we can annihilate
the Swarm in one blow!
But what about Yachiho?
She'll be fine.
The Sixth Squadron is in great hands.
They've got Tenka.
There's still two more humanoids?
Yes, ma 'am.
I can't see them now, but I'm sure.
Huh.
All right, then.
We'll take it from here.
I won't let you outshine me.
We'll give them something
better than an exhibition match.
We'll give them a commander showdown!
Roger!
Lady Ted and Lady Kyo are out
there fighting and I'm stuck here?
It's because the dorm has
the sturdiest barrier.
But I can barely see from
so far away, it's not fair!
I wanna watch, I wanna watch
their magnificence of gold!
Don't cry!
If you put your hand on Nae's shoulder,
she can link with your mind
so you can watch the fight!
Seriously?
Ms.
Okawamura, you're the best!
Yay, I can see them, this is awesome!
It's time to fall down!
Look at her go!
She's so amazing!
Shuki can't be beaten with normal weapons.
The power of Mato granted by the Peaches.
And specially made weapons
permeated with the Peaches' power?
are the only ways to counter them.
But the exception of that is Lady Kyo!
Kyoka Uzen!
She trained to top a
sacred mountain to perfect
her own unique style of
combat that destroys Shuki!
She gained the skills needed to defeat
them without relying on her Peach ability!
And this exceptional nature of hers is
how she landed her position as commander!
I can't believe I get to
see Lady Kyo's strength!
It's a dream come true for a fan like me!
Lady Kyo's ability is stronger than ever!
This is totally wicked!
Golden Hour!
Free for five seconds!
I'm not done yet!
Dammit, that's a lot of firepower!
This is what the humanoids are capable of?
Can't do that sneaky pose
of yours without an arm!
You're a fool!
One as elegant as I can pose no
matter how many limbs I have!
Golden Hour!
Rewind five seconds!
You're a persistent
little pest, aren't you?
My body's all warmed up.
I'll obliterate you with the next.
Nicely done, Yachi-ho.
That woman.
Where the hell did she come from?
Let's swap.
Go take it easy for a while.
Take it easy!
Well, my entire army's closing in.
You're gonna take a break?
What army's that?
I've already neutralized any Shuking.
That might interfere.
The reports reveal the existence of
two more officer-level humanoids.
But first, I would like to
start by eliminating you.
This power
It looks like I'm gonna get
to have a little fun tonight?
Thank you.
I love you.
I'll never leave you forever.
is required between each usage.
But if she passes out while it's active,
she'll lose her ability to
tell between friends and foes?
so it's best to cheer from afar.
Anyways, next time,
United Front Tinkasaur.